randomenthusiasm.com 2015-04-07

# Random Enthusiasm Privacy and Contact

To remove Random Enthusiasm from your Facebook:  
Click here: [Remove Random Enthusiasm](http://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=applications) and click the x to the right of Random Enthusiasm.

By using the Facebook application service provided by Random Enthusiasm, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information as outlined in this Privacy Policy. Please check this page periodically to be aware of any changes to this policy.

What We Collect

When you install an Random Enthusiasm Facebook application, Random Enthusiasm will collect your Facebook ID so we can identify you as a unique user of the app and allow you to interact with the app on Facebook. If you choose to share your email, we will store that as well. We may also collect basic information about you such as gender, age and location. 

How We Use Your Information

If you have shared your email address with us, we will use it to send you notifications of new content, and possibly to solicit feedback or input on our applications. Any emails sent will include a link to unsubscribe from the service. All "personally identifying information" that is collected will solely be used to determine demographic statistics on our applications for the purposes of advertising and improving our products. This personal information will never be shared with or sold to any third party. 

Content

All of our content is uploaded by our users or comes from sites that allow the embedding of images into the webpage (eg. imgur) and is in accordance with the DMCA. If there is any content on the site that should be removed please contact us at randomenthusiasm@gmail.com. 

Contact

If you have any further questions about this Privacy Policy, please email us at randomenthusiasm@gmail.com.
